http://www.buywax.com/privacy-policy

Menu CandlemakingFragrance OilsAll Fragrance OilsSample PackBest SellersNew FragrancesFruits & BerriesChristmasFood & BakingNatureDesignerFloralPoptails100% Natural FragrancesCost RevisedCloseoutPhthalate & Nitro Musk FreeVanillan FreeWaxSoy & NaturalSoy/Paraffin BlendContainerPillarTart WaxesVotiveMulti-PurposeCut & CarveGelGel WaxWax Fruit EmbedsGlass EmbedsColored Sandart SandSpaBeeswaxMicrocrystalineVybarsDuck & Cheese WaxesBeehive Dipping WaxesWax Hands WaxJars & LidsAztec Knox GlassOxford & CambridgeAll New GlassOxford StyleMedium SizeLarge SizeXL SizeCambridge StypleMedium SizeLarge SizeXL SizeDanube StyleCandle Making JarsCandle Making LidsCanning Lids (Have Seal)Metal TinsOverstock/Closeout JarWicksHow to Pick a WickPreTabbed WicksCotton Core Premier 700 Series Pre-Tabbed WicksZinc Core Pre-Tabbed WicksPaper Core Pre-Tabbed WicksHTP Pre-Tabbed WicksWooden WicksRaw WickingWick TabsMisc Wick AccessoriesDyesLiquid Candle DyeDye Blisters (Block)Candle Dye ChipsCut & Carve DyesClamShells and Tart MoldsAroma Beads & CrystalsCrystalsAdditivesMoldsTart MoldsMetal Pillar MoldsClam ShellsVotive MoldsTeaLightsSilicone Candle MoldsKitsBooksPackagingDipping BearsPotpourri & IncenseMiscellaneous Soap & LotionSkin Safe FragranceAllEssential Oil BlendsSample PackPhthalate & Nitro Musk FreeVanillan FreeMelt and Pour Glycerin Soap BasesNatural Melt and Pour BasesSLS FreeRegular Melt and Pour BasesCrafter's Choice SoapsCold Process Oils and ButtersBath & Body BasesLip BalmBasesSticks & PotsFlavorsAdditivesBottles & JarsBottles20/41022/40024/410JarsCaps20/41022/40024/410PumpsSprayersBooksColorantsDyes for Melt and Pour SoapsDyes for Cold Process Soap MakingGlittersBath Bomb Powder ColorSolid Color BarsStained Glass Color BarMatte Color BarNeon BarsMica Colorant BarsCrafter's Choice MicasNeonMoldsWooden Loaf MoldBath Bomb MoldsBasic GeometryBirds, Bees, & OthersCeltic DesignsGuest Size Soap MoldsTray MoldsHoliday MoldsSilicone Soap MoldsPackagingShrink WrapBoxesBath SaltsKitsPremixed CP Soap BaseLye (Sodium hydroxide)Equipment & ToolsEssential OilsAirome Essential OilsSingle Essential OilsEssential Oil BlendsEssential Oil Roll-OnsEssential Oil Gift SetsCBD Enhanced Essential OilsCBD Enhanced Essential Oil Roll-OnsCrafter's Choice Essential OilsDiffusers and WarmersDiffusersPluggable Diffusers - DiscontinuedUltraSonic DiffusersPorcelain DiffuserWarmers - Tart and CandleTart Warmers CaseIlluminationPlug-InGlimmerDish & WarmerBulbsTart Warmers SingleIlluminationPlug-InGlimmerDish & WarmerBulbsCandle Warmers CaseLampsCandle Warmers SingleLampsTart MoldsDiscontinuedDiscontinued 2017Discontinued 2018Candle Breeze WarmersCandle Breeze TinsNew WarmersHimalayan Salt LampsIlluminaire Fan Fragrance WarmersOverstock & DiscontinuedNew ItemsCanada
Account
Home
Candlemaking.com - Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Table Of Contents:
Our Commitment To Privacy
The Information We Collect
How We Use Information
Our Commitment To Data Security
Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy
How To Access Or Correct Your Information
How To Contact Us
Our Commitment To PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect:This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the BuyWax.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/Debit Card Information
(etc.)
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:
Name
Address
Phone Number
(etc.)
The Way We Use Information:We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data SecurityTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children’s PrivacyProtecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under
How You Can Access Or Correct Your InformationYou can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by [description of the company access procedure]. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact UsShould you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at1.800.369.5357 or send us an email at sales@candlemaking.com.
© 2020 Candle Making. All Rights Reserved. SITE MAP | PRIVACY POLICY
